Eyel Mordido

(519) 802-8975 eyelmordido@gmail.com eyelmordido.com linkedin.com/in/eyel-mordido

github.com/csmordido

PROFILE

A Front-End Web Developer with a background in Graphic Design and passion for learning. I bring my design knowledge and problem solving skills into projects to develop responsive and accessible websites that have seamless User Experience.

SKILLS































WORK EXPERIENCE

SC JOHNSON

Packaging Operator (Contract)

September 2018-March 2019

· Package and ensure quality of products. Assist in set up of equipment for different types of products, validate production records, troubleshoot machinery, and help train new employees.

KATAN STUDIOS

Graphic Designer (Contract)

July 2017-April 2018

- · Edited and retouched images in Photoshop, layout 20-40 page photo albums in InDesign and set up files for print.
- · Contacted clients about proofs and revised them as instructed.

NIKO APPAREL SYSTEMS

Graphic Designer

July 2016-July 2017

· Multi-tasked between layout and printing to meet tight deadlines of 20-25 orders a week. Implemented script in Illustrator to decrease layout time.

- · Designed mockups of sports jerseys and handled sublimation testing and colour matching.
- · Coordinated with clients and internal departments to ensure consistency of products with clients' expectations.
- · Designed website ads and trade show booth banners. Occasionally updated the company's Wordpress website.

FEATURED PROJECTS

MUSEUM FINDER React | JSX | CSS | GitHub



· A web app that allows tourists and people who love travelling find museums to visit.

TIDY DESK Javascript | HTML | SASS | ¡Query



· A hidden-object game requiring players to find objects in a list within 30 seconds.

EDUCATION

JUNO COLLEGE

Immersive Web Development Bootcamp May-July 2020 (9 weeks)

Part-time JavaScript Fundamentals November-December 2019

GEORGE BROWN COLLEGE Advanced Diploma in Graphic Design Major in Communication Design September 2011-April 2014

CENTENNIAL COLLEGE Certificate in Art & Design Foundation Studies January 2011-August 2011